Constitution Collection 6035
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Constitution Collection
1844-2010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kheel Center
6035
65 cubic feet
65 linear ft.
Records.
This is a collection of labor union constitutions.
5772835
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, November 05, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4197: Martin P. Catherwood Library American Labor Union Constitution and Proceedings Project Files 5405 mf: Switchmen's Union of North America Constitutions on Microfilm 5409 mf: Western Federation of Miners Constitutions on Microfilm 5410 mf: International Union of Mine, Mill, and Smelter Workers Constitutions on Microfilm 5427 mf: Knights of Labor Constitutions on Microfilm 5780/072: ILGWU Constitutions and Dues Books
Actors' Equity Association, Constitution, Archives; AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades Dept., Constitution, Archives; AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Dept., Constitution, Archives; AFL-CIO. Maritime Trades Dept., Constitution, Archives; AFL-CIO. Metal Trades Dept., Constitution, Archives; AFL-CIO. Railway Employees' Dept., Constitution, Archives; AFL-CIO. Union Label and Service Trades Dept., Constitution, Archives; Alabama State Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; Aluminum Workers International Union, Constitution, Archives; America Federation of Television and Radio Artists, Constitution, Archives; American Federation of Labor. Union Label Trades Dept., Constitution, Archives; American Federation of Labor. Metal Trades Dept., Constitution, Archives; American Guild of Musical Artists, Constitution, Archives; American Guild of Variety Artists, Constitution, Archives; Arizona State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Arkansas State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; California State Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; California State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Colorado State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations, Constitution, Archives; Connecticut State Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; Illinois Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; Indiana State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Iowa Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; Kansas Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; Massachusetts State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Michigan Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; Missouri Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; Missouri State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Montana Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; Montana State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Nebraska State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; New Mexico Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; New York State Industrial Union Council, Constitution, Archives; New York State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; North Carolina State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Ohio State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Oklahoma Federation of Labor, Constitution, Archives; Pennsylvania State Industrial Union Council, Constitution, Archives; Screen Actors Guild; South Carolina State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Tennessee State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; Virginia State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives; West Virginia State. AFL-CIO, Constitution, Archives
5772835
- American Federation of Labor, 1936-1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- AFL Building and Construction Trades Dept., 1933-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  1933-1954, 1965
- AFL Union Label Dept., 1904-1955 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- AFL Metal Trades Dept., 1912-1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- AFL Mining Dept., 1912-1914 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- AFL Railway Employees Dept., 1911-1938 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  1911, 1938
- AFL Women's International Union Label League, 1927-1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  1927, 1950
- AFL Women's Auxiliaries, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- AFL Federal Labor Unions, 1934-1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- AFL Alabama State Federation of Labor, 1938-1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- AFL Arizona State Federation of Labor, 1916-1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  1916, 1938-1954
- AFL Arkansas State Federation of Labor, 1926-1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  1926, 1940, 1951
- AFL California State Federation of Labor, 1909-1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- AFL Colorado State Federation of Labor, 1911-1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- AFL Connecticut State Federation of Labor, 1937-1957 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- AFL Delaware State Federation of Labor, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- AFL Florida State Federation of Labor, 1926-1951 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  1926, 1948, 1951
- AFL Idaho State Federation of Labor, 1918-1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  1918, 1940, 1977
- AFL Illinois State Federation of Labor, 1912-1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  1912, 1936-1957, 1971
- AFL Iowa State Federation of Labor, 1927-1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  1927, 1940-1954
- AFL Kansas State Federation of Labor, 1916-1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  1916, 1953-1964
- AFL Kentucky State Federation of Labor, 1949-1953 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- AFL Louisiana State Federation of Labor, 1938-1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- AFL Maine State Federation of Labor, 1926-1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  1926-1934, 1953
- AFL Maryland State Federation of Labor, 1926 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- AFL Massachusetts State Federation of Labor, 1923-1954 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- AFL Michigan State Federation of Labor, 1914-1956 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  1914, 1927, 1938-1956
- AFL Minnesota State Federation of Labor, 1911-1956 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  1911-1921, 1950-1956
- AFL Mississippi State Federation of Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- AFL Missouri State Federation of Labor, 1937-1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- AFL Montana State Federation of Labor, 1927-1952 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- AFL Nebraska State Federation of Labor, 1941-1954 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- AFL Nevada State Federation of Labor, 1921-1938 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  1921, 1938
- AFL New Hampshire State Federation of Labor, 1928-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  1928, 1940-1962, 1977
- AFL New Jersey State Federation of Labor, 1922-1936 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  1922, 1936
- AFL New Mexico State Federation of Labor, 1926-1951 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- AFL New York State Federation of Labor, 1924-1947 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- AFL Ohio State Federation of Labor, 1940-1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  1940-1948, 1976
- AFL Oklahoma State Federation of Labor, 1917-1951 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  1917-1931, 1949-1951
- AFL Oregon State Federation of Labor, 1927 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- AFL Pennsylvania State Federation of Labor, 1913-1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  1913-1929, 1949-1955, 1975, 1978
- AFL Puerto Rico Federation Libre, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- AFL South Carolina State Federation of Labor, 1940-1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- AFL South Dakota State Federation of Labor, 1936-1956 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  1936, 1951-1956
- AFL Tennessee State Federation of Labor, 1950-1953 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- AFL Texas State Federation of Labor, 1921-1953 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  1921, 1938-43, 1952-1953
- AFL Vermont State Federation of Labor, 1947-1952 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- AFL Virginia State Federation of Labor, 1933-1941 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- AFL Washington State Federation of Labor, 1927-1959 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  1927-1929, 1947-1959
- AFL West Virginia State Federation of Labor, 1922-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  1922-1926, 1947-1959, 1969
- AFL Wyoming State Federation of Labor, 1927-1938 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  1927, 1938
- Binghamton, NY and Vicinity, Central Labor Union of, 1942-1952 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Buffalo, NY and Vicinity, Federation of Labor of, 1938-1945 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Chicago Federation of Labor, 1906-1951 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  1906, 1946-1951
- Cleveland Federation of Labor, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Dunkirk, NY Central Labor Council (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Elmira, NY Central Trades & Labor Assembly, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Ithaca, NY Central Labor Union, 1940-1950 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Milwaukee and Vicinity Federated Trades Council, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- New Orleans Federation of Labor, 1936 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- New York, NY Central Federated Union, 1900 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- New York and Vicinity, Central Trades and Labor Council of Greater, 1886-1930 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  1886, 1930
- Rochester, NY Central Trades & Labor Council, 1935-1951 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  1935, 1951
- San Bernadino Central Labor Council (Box 3, Folder 23)
- San Francisco, CA Labor Council, 1904-1951 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  1904, 1951
- Solano County Central Labor Council, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Troy, NY Federation of Labor, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Utica, NY Federation of Labor, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Utica, NY Trade and Labor Assembly, 1902-1908 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Committee for Industrial Organization, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1938-1955 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Alabama CIO Council, 1948-1955 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- California CIO Council, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- California State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1956 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Colorado State Industrial Union Council, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Connecticut State Industrial Union Council, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Delaware State Industrial Union Council, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Florida State Industrial Union Council, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Georgia State Industrial Union Council, 1946-1956 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Illinois State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  1950, 1954
- Indiana State Industrial Union Council, 1938-1950 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Iowa State Industrial Union Council, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Louisiana State Industrial Union Council, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Maine State Industrial Union Council, 1942-1953 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  1942, 1953
- Maryland State Industrial Union Council, 1938-1952 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  1938, 1950, 1952
- Massachusetts State Industrial Union Council, 1949-1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  1949, 1953
- Michigan State Industrial Union Council, 1906-1953 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  1906, 1944-1953
- Minnesota State Industrial Union Council, 1953-1959 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  1953, 1959
- Nebraska State Industrial Union Council, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- New Jersey State Industrial Union Council, 1942-1955 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- New York State Industrial Union Council, 1939-1954 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Ohio State Industrial Union Council, 1940-1955 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  1940, 1950-1955
- Oregon State Industrial Union Council, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Pennsylvania State Industrial Union Council, 1938-1957 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Puerto Rico, Federacion Libre de old Trabajadores, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- South Carolina State Industrial Union Council, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Tennessee State Industrial Union Council, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  1950, 1953
- Texas State Industrial Union Council, 1940-1951 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  1940, 1951
- Utah State Industrial Union Council, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Virginia State Industrial Union Council, 1940-1953 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  1940, 1953
- Washington State Industrial Union Council, 1941-1954 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  1941, 1950, 1954
- West Virginia State Industrial Union Council, 1944-1953 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Buffalo Industrial Union Council, 1945-1954 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  1945, 1954
- New York City CIO Council, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Greater NY Industrial Union Council, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- San Francisco Labor Council, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Schenectady Area Industrial Union Council, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Wayne County CIO Council, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Westchester County CIO Council, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- AFL-CIO, 1955-2005 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Auxiliaries, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Building & Construction Trades Dept., 1965-1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Federal Labor Unions, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Food and Beverage Trades Dept., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Government Emp. Council, 1958-1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Industrial Union Dept. AFL-CIO, 1955-1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Joint Unity Committee, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Maritime Trades Dept., 1960-1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  1960-1983, 1997
- AFL-CIO Metal Trades Dept., 1955-1985 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  1955-1963, 1975-1985
- AFL-CIO Professional Emp. Dept. of, 1979-2005 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  1979, 1997, 2003-2005
- AFL-CIO Public Emp. Dept., 1981-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO Railway Emp. Dept., 1956-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Scientific, Professional and Cultural, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Union Label & Service Dept., 1959-1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Alabama State, 1956-1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Arkansas State, 1956-1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Arizona State, 1959-1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO California State, 1966-2000 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Colorado State, 1956-1975 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Connecticut State, 1959-1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  1959, 1974
- AFL-CIO Delaware State, 1962-1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  1962, 1974
- AFL-CIO Florida State, 1961-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO Georgia State, 1957-1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO Idaho State, 1958-1976 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Illinois State, 1958-1967 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Indiana State, 1958-1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Iowa State, 1958-1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO Kansas State, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Kentucky State, 1959-1984 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- AFL-CIO Louisiana State, 1964-1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Maine State, 1953-1964 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Maryland State and District of Columbia (Box 7, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Massachusetts State, 1958-1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Michigan State, 1958-1976 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO Minnesota State, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Mississippi State, 1962-1971 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO Missouri State, 1956-1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO Missouri State Labor Council, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Montana State, 1956-1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Nebraska State, 1956-1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO Nevada State, 1957-1971 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  1957, 1971
- AFL-CIO New Hampshire State, 1963-1974 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- AFL-CIO New Jersey State, 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- AFL-CIO New Mexico State, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO New York City, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO New York State, 1965-1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO New York State, 1956-1996 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- AFL-CIO North Carolina State, 1960-1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO North Dakota State, 1957-1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  1957, 1972-1976
- AFL-CIO Ohio State, 1960-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- AFL-CIO Oklahoma State, 1957-1959 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Oregon State, 1956-1972 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Pennsylvania State, 1960-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO Rhode Island State, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- AFL-CIO South Carolina State, 1957-1974 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- AFL-CIO Tennessee State, 1955-1975 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- AFL-CIO Texas State, 1961-1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- AFL-CIO Utah State, 1963-1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Vermont State, 1956-1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Virginia State, 1956-1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- AFL-CIO Washington State, 1960-1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  1960-1962, 1974-1976
- AFL-CIO West Virginia State, 1958-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- AFL-CIO Wyoming State, 1964-1972 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  1964, 1972
- AFL-CIO Broome County, NY Federation of Labor, 1960-1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  1960, 1975
- AFL-CIO Buffalo AFL-CIO Council, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- AFL-CIO Chemung County, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Los Angeles County Federation of Labor, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Actors and Artists, 1965-1992 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  1965, 1978, 1992
- Actors and Artists, Actors' Equity Assoc., 1949-1996 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  1949-1974, 1980-1996
- Actors and Artists, American Guild of Musical Artists, 1947-1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Actors and Artists, American Guild of Variety Artists, 1963-1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  1963, 1973
- Actors and Artists of America Assoc., Radio Artists, American Federation of, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Actors and Artists, Screen Actors Guild, 1945-2007 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Actors and Artists, Screen Extras Guild, 1954-1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Actors and Artists, American Federation of TV & Radio Artists, 1948-1984 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Actors and Artists, Variety Artists, American Guild of, 1939-1973 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Afro-American Labor Council National, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Workers, 1951-1952 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Airline Communication Employees Assoc., 1952 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Airline Dispatchers Assoc., 1939-1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Airline Employees Assoc., 1975-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Airline Mechanics Assoc., 1943 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Airline Pilots International Assoc., 1950-2002 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Airline Stewards and Stewardesses, 1953-1957 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Air Traffic Controllers Association National, 1990-2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Allied & Technical Workers of the U.S. & Canada; Int'l Union of District 50, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Allied Industrial Workers of America, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Aluminum, Brick & Clay Workers International Union, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Aluminum, Brick & Glass Workers International Union, 1983-1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Aluminum Workers International Union, 1940-1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Aluminum Workers of America, 1940-1942 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- American Federation of Musicians, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- American Federation of School Administrators, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, AFL-CIO, 1988-1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  1988, 1994
- American Federation of Teachers, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- American Flint Glass Workers' Union of North America, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- American Guild of Musical Artists, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- American Guild of Variety Artists, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- American Nurses Association, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- American Postal Workers Union, 1986-1994 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  1986, 1994
- Arsenal Workers, National, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Asbestos Workers, International Assoc. of Heat and Frost Insulators, 1937-1997 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Associated Unions of America, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Australian Workers Union, 1970-1977 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Impl. Workers (UAW), 1943-1983 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- UAW, 1986-2004 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Authors League of American, Dramatics Guild, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- UAW, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- UAW, 1941-1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  1941-1953, 1989
- Bakers and Confectioners Int'l Union of American; Journeymen, 1901-1917 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  1901, 1917
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers Union, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers, International Union of America, 1912-1974 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Bakery and Confectionery Workers, International Union America, 1958-1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Bakery, Confectionery and Tobacco Workers International Union, 1978-1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Barber and Beauty Culturists Union of American, 1942-1952 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Barbers, Beauticians and Allied Industries International Assoc., 1974-1979 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Barbers, Hairdressers, and Cosmetologists International Union of America, Journeymen, 1954-1964 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Barbers International Union of America, Journeymen, 1902-1942 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Barbers of America, Associated Master, 1927 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Baseball Players Assoc., Major League, 1967-1976 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Bill Posters, Billers & Distributors, International Alliance of, 1946 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Blacksmiths, Drop Forgers & Helpers, International Brotherhood of, 1927-1947 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Boiler Makers, Brotherhood of, 1903 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Boiler Makers, Iron Ship Builders & Helpers of America, International Brotherhood of, 1906-1930 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Bookbinders, International Brotherhood of, 1912-1964 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Brass Workers of NYC and Vicinity, Amalgamated, 1890 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Brewers & Coopers Sick Benefit Assoc., 1899 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Brewers of the U.S. National Union of, 1886-1887 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Brewery Workers Union of New York & Vicinity, 1881 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Brewery Workmen of American, International Union United, 1917-1930 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Brewery Workmen of U.S. National Union of United, 1887-1903 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink & Distillery Workers of America, International Union, 1917-1977 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Brick and Clay Workers of America, United, 1920-1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Brick, Tile and Terra Cotta Workers' Alliance, International, 1909-1913 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Bricklayers and Allied Craftsmen, International Union of, 1975-2005 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Bricklayers and Masons International Union of America, 1901-1908 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International Union of America, 1898-1968 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Bricklayers, Masons and Plasterers International Union of America -, 1900-1940 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Broadcast Employees and Technicians, 1952-1995 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Broom and Whisk Makers' International, 1942-1946 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Labor, 1900 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Building and Construction Trades Council of Greater New York and Vicinity, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Building and General Laborers' International Protective Union of America, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Building Trades Council of North America, National, 1901-1902 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Butcher Workmen of America, Brotherhood of, 1907 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- California State Employees Assoc., 1976-1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Canada, Alberta Federation of Labor, 1947-1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Canada, British Columbia, 1962-2006 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Canada, Canadian Brotherhood of Railway, Transport, and General Workers, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Canada, Manitoba Federation of Labor, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Canada, New Brunswick Federation of Labor, 1975-2000 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  1975-1987, 2000
- Canada, Nova Scotia Federation of Labor, 1961-1968 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Canada, Ontario Federation of Labor, 1951-2007 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Canada, Policemen's Brotherhood of Montreal, 1966-2002 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  1966-1976, 1999-2002
- Canada, Quebec Federation of Labor, 1959-1962 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Canadian Congress of Labor, 1947-1955 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Canadian Labor Congress, 1966-1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Canadian Union of Public Employees, 1971-2009 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Cannery, Agricultural Packing, 1937-1942 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Canada, Saskatchewan Federation of Labor, 1959-2006 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Canada, Confederation of National Trade Unions, 1963-1975 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Canada, New Democratic Party, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Canada, Seafarers International Union of Canada, 1956-1986 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Canada Trades & Labor Congress, 1948-1954 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Carpenters & Joiners, Amalgamated Society of, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Carpenters & Joiners of America, United Brotherhood of, 1907-1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Carpenters & Joiners, United Brotherhood of, 1888 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Carpenters Protective Assoc. House (New York State), 1844 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Catholic Trade Unionists, Assoc. of, 1940-1955 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Cement, Lime & Gypsum Workers International Union, United, 1964-1980 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Cement Workers, Amalgamated Brotherhood of, 1909-1913 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Chemical and Allied Industries Unions, International Council of, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 3)